American Association for Labor Legislation Pamphlet File 5001 PAM
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 6, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: History of the Two Years' Campaign of the Committee on Factories, 1913; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Medical Economics, 1913; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Minutes of Meeting, 1915; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Official Notice to all Registrars of Vital Statistics, Subregistrars, Physicians, Midwives, Undertakers, and Persons in Charge of Cemeteries, 1915; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Program of the Forty-Third Annual Meeting of the American Public Health Association, 1915; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Minutes of Meeting of Sub-Committee on Investigations and Advisors to Sub-Committee, 1915; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: Minutes of meeting of the Committee on Alcohol, 1915; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: Meeting of subcommittee on Social Service of Advisory Committee on Municipal Lodging House, 1915; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: Minutes of Meeting Sub-Committee on National, State and Municipal policies, 1915; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: The State and the Coal Supply Prices, Pay, Profits, 1911; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Author: Tom Myers
  - Item 14: The Present Condition of Public Health Organization in the United States, Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Author: Prof. Selskar M. Gunn
  - Item 15: An Address Before the Annual Meeting, 1915; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Author: Hon. S.S. Goldwater
  - Item 16: Minutes of Meeting, 1915; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Box: 6, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Methods of Investigation in Social and Health Problems, 1917; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Author: Donald B. Armstrong, Franz Schneider, Louis Dublin
  - Item 2: For Your Information, 1917; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Preventive Medicine and Birth Control, 1917; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Author: S. Adolphus Knopf
  - Item 4: Minutes of a Meeting, 1916; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Weekly Bulletin, 1916; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Notes: January 29, 1916
  - Item 6: Program Twelfth Annual Meeting, 1916; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Notes: May 11-12, 1916
  - Item 7: Some of the Larger Problems of the Medical Profession, 1916; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Author: Rupert Blue
    Notes: June 17, 1916
  - Item 8: Health First- How We Can Insure It, 1916; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: Address by the Chairman, 1916; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Notes: February 25, 1916
  - Item 10: Minutes of a Meeting, 1916; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Item 11: The Crusader, 1917; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Item 12: Weekly Bulletin, 1917; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Item 13: How to Live, 1918; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Notes: March 1918
  - Item 14: Military Medicine and Surgery, 1918; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Item 15: The Examination of Registrants, 1918; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Author: M.L. Harris
  - Item 16: Dispensary Applying War Lessons to Industry, 1918; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Author: John Howard Ransom
  - Item 17: Looking After Ohio Soldiers Discharged for Tuberculosis, 1918; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Item 18: Banking Expert Urges Health as Thrift Fundamental, 1918; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Item 19: Medical Mobilization and the War, 1918; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Item 20: The Del Monte Meeting, 1918; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Item 21: Health Survey of Middletown Connecticut, 1918; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Author: David Greenberg and Ira D. Joel
- Box: 6, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Automobile Fatalities, 1920; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
    Author: Frederick S. Crum
  - Item 2: Tetra Ethyl Lead A New Health Danger to Workers, 1925; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Health News, 1924; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: How to Live, 1923; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: What Price this Freedom, 1924; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: The Physical Examination of Well Persons, 1922; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
    Author: Eugene Lyman Fisk
  - Item 7: Programme, 1921; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
    Notes: New York City
  - Item 8: Publications, 1921; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Item 9: Minutes of Meeting, 1919; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
    Notes: May 28, 1919
  - Item 10: Resignation of Chairman of Committee and Appointment of Successor, 1919; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Item 11: Recommendation Concerning the Prevention of Anthrax, 1919; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Item 12: Foreign Correspondence, 1919; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Item 13: Stated Meeting, 1919; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
    Notes: February 18, 1919
  - Item 14: Minutes of Meeting, 1919; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
    Notes: May 27, 1919
  - Item 15: Memorandum, 1919; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Item 16: One Hundred Health Exhibits, 1920; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
    Notes: September 1, 1920
  - Item 17: Investigations Regarding Health in Industry, 1923; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
    Author: Wade Wright and Florence Crowell
  - Item 18: Announcement, 1921; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Item 19: Health Fortnight, 1921; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Item 20: A Health Center Plan, 1921; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Item 21: T.B. The Terror of the Tenements, 1921; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Item 22: Newsletter, 1921; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Item 23: Medical News, 1922; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Item 24: Employers Indemnity Corporation, 1922; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
    Author: E.G. Trimble
  - Item 25: Statement of the Board of Directors, 1924; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Item 26: Meeting of the Boston Advisory Council of the Life Extension Institute, 1925; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Item 27: Minutes of Meeting, 1923; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
    Notes: September 26, 1923
  - Item 28: A Correction of Misstatements About the Life Extension Institute, 1925; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Box: 6, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Guardians of the Nation's Health, 1927; Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: The Common Cold, 1931; Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Notes: January 1931
  - Item 3: The Great Need in Influenza, 1931; Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Notes: February 1931
  - Item 4: What Periodic Health Examinations Reveal, 1931; Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Notes: March 1931
  - Item 5: Clothing the Body to Meet Seasonal Changes, 1931; Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Notes: April 1931
  - Item 6: Conscious Training in Relaxation, 1931; Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Notes: May 1931
  - Item 7: The Eye in Relation to General Health, 1931; Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Notes: June 1931
  - Item 8: Heart Disease and Mental Strain, 1931; Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Notes: July 1931
  - Item 9: In Memoriam Dr. Eugene Lyman Fisk, 1931; Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Notes: August 1931
  - Item 10: Importance of Routine X-Ray Examination of the Chest, 1931; Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Item 11: How to Live, 1931; Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Notes: December 1931
  - Item 12: How to Live, 1932; Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Item 13: How to Live, 1932; Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Notes: March 1932
  - Item 14: How to Live, 1932; Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Notes: June 1932
  - Item 15: How to Live, 1932; Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Notes: July 1932
  - Item 16: How to Live, 1932; Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Notes: October 1932
  - Item 17: How to Live, 1932; Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Notes: December 1932
  - Item 18: Annual Report of the President to the Board of Directors, 1930; Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Item 19: General Budget for 1928, Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Item 20: Social Welfare, 1929; Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Item 21: Laboratory Technicians and the Public Health, 1931; Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Author: George H. Trafton
  - Item 22: Dinner Meeting What Statistics Contribute in Public Health, 1932; Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Notes: January 29, 1932
  - Item 23: Divisions and Institutions, 1936; Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Item 24: Health Security and the American Public, 1936; Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Author: Michael M. Davis and Dr. Morris Fishbein
    Notes: March 5, 1936
- Box: 6, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The University Forum, 1937; Publication (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Reports of a Committee, 1928; Publication (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Notes: May 15, 1928
  - Item 3: A Half Century of Public Health, 1921; Publication (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Past, Present, and Future, 1937; Publication (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Operations during Year 1939, 1940; Publication (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: Abstract of Proceedings, 1939; Publication (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Box: 6, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Who we Are. What We Stand For. What We Are Doing., Publication (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Periodic Health Examinations, 1928; Publication (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: General Committees, Publication (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Provisional Program for the 1916 Meeting, Publication (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Monthly Health Letter, 1917; Publication (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: Medical Mobilization and the War, Publication (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: Special Course in District Maternity Nursing for Undergraduate Students, Publication (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Item 8: Budget by Projects, 1927; Publication (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Item 9: Corn-Shredder Guards, Publication (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Item 10: Questions & Answers, Publication (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Item 11: Rules of Life, Publication (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Item 12: Working for You, Publication (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Item 13: The Treatment of Gonorrhea, Publication (Box 6, Folder 15)
    Author: William J. Robinson
  - Item 14: The Limitation of Offspring, Publication (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Item 15: Special Bulletin on Infantile Paralysis, Publication (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Item 16: Designed as a Self-Supporting Philanthropy, Publication (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Item 17: Pneumococcemia; Bilateral Empyema; Recovery, Publication (Box 6, Folder 15)
    Author: Edward A. Aronson and Harry Olsan
  - Item 18: How You Can Help Save Human Lives, Publication (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Item 19: Hygiene Reference Board, Publication (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Box: 6, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Nourishing Food a Necessity, Publication (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Questionnaire by Committee on Tuberculosis in Industry, Publication (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Minutes Advisory Committee, Publication (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Suggestions, 1915; Publication (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: The Proposed County Health Center, 1921; Publication (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Box: 6, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: For Prevention of Railroad Strikes, 1916; Publication (Box 6, Folder 17)
    Notes: September 1916
  - Item 2: Memorandum Railway Pension Costs and Accounting, 1927; Publication (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Transportation Act 1920, Publication (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Act Now, Publication (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: Another Rubaiyat, Publication (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: Occupation Hazard of Locomotive Firemen, Publication (Box 6, Folder 17)
    Author: Henry J. Harris
- Box: 6, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: How to Prevent Accidents, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: The Mechanical Engineer and Prevention of Accidents, 1911; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
    Author: John Calder
  - Item 3: The Employer and Prevention of Accidents, 1911; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Industrial Accident Prevention, 1911; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
    Author: R.W. Campbell
  - Item 5: First Cooperative Safety Congress, 1912; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Prevention a Benefaction Compensation an Apology, 1910; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: Special Issue describing the Award of the Scientific American Gold Medal, 1910; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: Governor's Special Message Transmitting Report of the Industrial Commission, 1909; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 9: Elevators are Death Traps, 1910; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 10: Casualties to Trainmen, 1909; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 11: Casualties to Trainmen, 1909; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 12: Tons of Freight Carried One Mile per Trainmen Employed, 1909; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 13: Interstate Commerce Commission, 1910; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
    Notes: February 1910
  - Item 14: A Review of Accident Prevention and Relief, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 15: McArthur's Portable Fire Escape and Jacob's Ladder, 1908; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 16: The Reporting of Industrial Diseases, 1912; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 17: Safety Standards through State Inspection, 1911; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
    Author: Edgar T. Davies
  - Item 18: To the Rescue, 1910; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 19: Catalogue of the Exposition of Safety Devices and Industrial Hygiene, 1908; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 20: Report of the Director to the President and Board, 1910; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 21: Perils of Peace; or a Safer America, 1909; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
    Author: William H. Tolman
  - Item 22: Death Traps Could be Made Safe-How?, 1910; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 23: Manuals of Safety Alcoholism in Industry, 1911; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 24: Seven Rules for Shop Safety, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 25: Questions for Conductors and Motormen, 1909; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 26: Safety of Employees and Travelers Upon Railroads, 1910; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 27: Report of Investigation of Three Hundred Industrial Accidents in Kansas City, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 28: Abstract of Proposed Amendments, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 29: Bakery Inspection and Proceedings, 1908; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 30: Education in Accident Prevention, 1912; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
    Author: Melville W. Mix
  - Item 31: First Public Hearing, 1911; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 32: Report on the Fire Hazard, 1912; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Box: 6, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Industrial Accidents in the United States and their Relative Frequency in Different Occupations, 1914; Publication (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Safety as a Part of the Education of an Engineer, 1914; Publication (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Minutes of the Meeting of the Committee on Dangerous Trades and Processes, 1913; Publication (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: Accident Report, 1913; Publication (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Item 5: Accident Prevention Work, 1913; Publication (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Item 6: Accident Prevention on the Farm, 1914; Publication (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Item 7: The Prevention of Industrial Accidents, 1914; Publication (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Item 8: The Prevention of Industrial Accidents, 1910; Publication (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Item 9: The Prevention of Accidents, 1914; Publication (Box 6, Folder 19)
    Author: Ferd C. Schwedtman
  - Item 10: Accident Prevention, Publication (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Item 11: Health and Safety The Universal Danger Sign, 1914; Publication (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Item 12: Safety and Sanitation, 1913; Publication (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Item 13: Autocrat Eye Protectors and Respirating Devices, 1913; Publication (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Item 14: Standard Safety Devices, 1914; Publication (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Item 15: Tabulation of Causes of Accidents, 1913; Publication (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Item 16: Rules, Requirements, and Universal Safety Standards, 1914; Publication (Box 6, Folder 19)
    Notes: February 1914
- Box: 6, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention, 1917; Publication (Box 6, Folder 20)
    Author: Barney Cohen
  - Item 2: A Safety First Lecture, 1915; Publication (Box 6, Folder 20)
    Notes: May 14, 1915
  - Item 3: Report of Committee on Analysis of Accidents, 1916; Publication (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: The Prevention of Accidents in Cotton Mills, 1915; Publication (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Item 5: First Annual Industrial Safety Exposition of Ohio, 1915; Publication (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Item 6: International Association of Industrial Accident Boards and Commissions, 1916; Publication (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Item 7: Diamond Candy Company Factory Fire Holocaust, 1915; Publication (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Item 8: Sanitary Code for Laundries, 1916; Publication (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Item 9: Labor Law Factory Exit Provision Held Constitutional, 1917; Publication (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Item 10: General Safety Orders, 1916; Publication (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Item 11: Logging and Sawmill Safety Orders, 1917; Publication (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Item 12: Sanitary Standards for the Felt Hating Industry, 1915; Publication (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Item 13: General Construction Safety Orders, 1918; Publication (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Item 14: Report, 1915; Publication (Box 6, Folder 20)
    Author: Laurence M.D. McGuire
- Box: 7, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Safety Convention and Annual General Meeting, 1928; Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Minutes of the Conference on Proposed Safety Rules for Construction Industries, 1928; Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Organizations Invited to Port Safety Conference, 1928; Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Recommedations for Safety Rules for Stevedoring Operations Aboard Ship, 1928; Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Seattle Maritime Safety Rules, 1928; Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: What Accident Prevention Can Do, 1928; Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: What Is Being Done for Safety in Canada- The Work of the Industrial Accident Prevention Associations, 1928; Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Many Deaths Reported in Construction in November, 1929; Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Author: Bureau of Statistics and Information
  - Item 9: Industrial Fatalities Number 202 in October, 1929; Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Governor's Council Meeting, 1928; Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Analysis of Stevedore Accident Prevention, 1928; Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Proposed international regulations and conventions, 1928; Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: American Recommended Practice Underground Transportation in Metal Mines, 1928; Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: American Recommended Practice in Mechnical Loading in Metal Mines, 1928; Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Memorandum for Safety Conference, 1928; Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Report of the Secretary of the IAIA Boards and Commissions to the 15th Annual Meeting, 1928; Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Author: Bureau of Labor Statistics
  - Item 17: Conference on Proposed Port Safety Code, 1928; Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: Minutes of Preliminary Conference on the Proposal for a National Port Safety Code, 1928; Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Box: 7, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Is there an Accident Prone Employee?, 1930; Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Author: C.B. Auel
  - Item 2: Meeting of Committee on Safety, 1930; Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Weekly Bulletin, 1929; Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Author: Department of Health
  - Item 4: Information Circular, 1929; Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Author: Bureau of Mines
  - Item 5: Governor's Council Meeting, 1929; Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Pacific Coast Safety Code Stevedoring Operations on Board Ship, 1929; Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Safety Code for Coal Mine Transportation, 1930; Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Meeting of the Mining Standardization Correlating Committee, 1930; Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Compressed Air Work Rules, 1930; Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Author: Office of Assistant Commissioner
  - Item 10: Proposed Rules and Regulations Covering Compressed Air Work, 1930; Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Box: 7, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Report of Committee of Award, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Author: John M. Flynn
  - Item 2: The Psychology of the Causes and Prevention of Accidents, 1919; Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Author: Martin J. Flyzik
  - Item 3: The Manufacturers' Contribution to State-Wide Safety, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Preventing Eye Injuries, 1932; Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Detective Vision- A Cause of Accidents, 1932; Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Safety Through the Prevention of Accidents, 1932; Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: American Recommended Practice, 1932; Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Report of the Director of the Bureau of Safety to the Interstate Commerce Commission, 1933; Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Abstracts of Bureau Publications, 1933; Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Commissioners Attending, 1933; Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Objects, 1933; Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Box: 7, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Injuries in the Home How they are Caused and How they can be Prevented, 1935; Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Facts and Figures on Home and Farm Accident Prevention, 1935; Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Fifth Annual State-wide Industrial Safety Conference, 1934; Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Saving Lives Through a Drivers License Law, 1935; Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: For Immediate Release Federal Coordinator of Transportation, 1935; Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Box: 7, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Home and Farm Accident Prevention, 1935; Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Too Long at the Wheel, 1935; Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: 1929 Address by Howard S. Cullman, 1935; Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Injuries in the Home and on the Farm, 1936; Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Group Discussion Material on Accident Prevention, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: American Mutual Magazine, 1935; Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Box: 7, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: How Long on the Highway, 1937; Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Annual Report, 1937; Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Principal Safety Promotion Adviser, 1937; Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - 1937, Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Comparison of Drafts of Proposed Safety Code for Coal Mine Ventilation, 1937; Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Responsibility of Labor and Management in the Field of Accident Prevention, 1938; Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Memorandum for Mr. George Keogh, 1938; Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Greater Safety in the Coal Mining Industry, 1938; Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)